welcome to a short video botas yes for
欢迎观看简短的视频botas，是的
bootleg hammers for remote apps so by
远程应用的盗版锤，因此
now you should have learned from another
现在你应该从另一个中学到
video good life hovers for local apps
本地应用的视频美好生活盘旋
how useful the herb or troubleshooting
草药或故障排除的有用性
your springboard application so the same
您的跳板应用程序也是如此
feature exists for remote spring boot
存在用于远程弹簧启动的功能
apps so it's activated when you deploy
应用程序，以便在部署时将其激活
your spring boot app to CF and the
您的 spring boot 应用程序到CF和
deployment dialog at the bottom you see
您将在底部看到部署对话框
this GM access a channel enabled
该GM访问已启用的频道
checkbox so if you check mark it enable
复选框，如果您选中它，则启用它
it then there will be an incisional
然后会有一个切开
between your ID and your remote app on
在您的ID和您的远程应用之间
CF and we have the tunnel the live data
CF，我们拥有实时数据通道
beans well the data about like beans
bean 很好关于 bean 的数据
will be fetched into your ID I have
将被提取到您拥有的ID中
already deployed my app on CF with Jam
已经用Jam在CF上部署了我的应用程序
expositional enabled as you can tell
正如您所知，启用了博览会
from this little gmx tag here the the
从这里的小gmx标签开始
Apple so has remote boot dev tools
苹果公司因此拥有远程启动开发工具
attached to it so we can see the life
附加到它，所以我们可以看到生活
good life handsome and hundreds already
美好的生活，英俊而已
as always cold lands is enabled so it's
一如既往地启用了冷地，因此
the covers are exactly the same as for
封面与完全相同
almost the same as for local apps the
与本地应用程序几乎相同
only difference here is for example this
唯一的区别是例如
process information able process on CF
CF上具有过程信息能力的过程
rather than local process and if the
而不是本地流程，如果
request mappings you get obviously the
请求映射，您显然会得到
the CF URL rather than local URL so if
CF URL而不是本地URL，所以如果
we navigate let's say to our home page
我们导航到我们的主页
of the app and you can see that's
的应用程序，您可以看到
working and it's coming from CM alright
工作，它是从CM好吧
so there is a problem with the app which
因此该应用存在问题
is if you look for all there is it
如果你寻找所有的东西
doesn't find any owners but there must
找不到任何所有者，但必须
be son so we should try and fix that
是儿子，所以我们应该尝试并解决这个问题
using
使用
bootleg Hansen hungries so that was the
盗版汉森饿了，所以那是
older standpoint so let's let me give
较旧的立场，让我给
you this point
你这一点
right the problem is here although
是的，问题出在这里
search service returns empty results so
搜索服务返回空结果，因此
let's see what it's defined it goes in
让我们看看它的定义
we have the satyr and the seller is auto
我们有色狼，卖家是汽车
wire it we could see that being being
连线，我们可以看到
wired in here is empty only research
接线在这里是空的，只有研究
service which which is kind of
那种服务
self-explanatory if you look at the
不言而喻，如果你看
implementation and also it transcends
实施，也超越
the list so you should see where this
列表，所以你应该看到这个
pin is defined and why it ends up in the
引脚已定义，以及为什么会终止于
application context so I should look at
应用程序上下文，所以我应该看一下
its resource so the resource is really
它的资源，所以资源真的
well the place where it's defined is
定义的地方是
really this abdi notation and we could
真的是这个阿卜迪语符号，我们可以
see that's injected into older
看到这注入了老
controller so that's the right place so
控制器，所以在正确的地方
empty only search service relative
仅空搜索服务相对
properties is search is false so
属性是搜索是错误的，所以
properties is another being being
属性是另一个存在
authorized in in our only configuration
在我们唯一的配置中获得授权
so let's look at the type all those
让我们来看看所有这些类型
properties and figure out what's what's
属性并找出什么是什么
here so it's a configuration properties
这是配置属性
been with products that clinical
与临床产品一起使用
medicine defines the search properties
医学定义了搜索属性
authors and externalize that clinic
作者并外部化该诊所
owners search property that by default
所有者搜索默认情况下的属性
is holes so let's set this property to
是孔，所以我们将此属性设置为
true it's not only in the properties
是的，不仅在属性中
file in the yellow file so let's define
黄色文件中的文件，所以让我们定义
it so to true and let's go back to our
如此真实，让我们回到我们的
older controller beam and see if the
较旧的控制器光束，看是否
right beam is being injected now right
现在正在注入右光束
and it just got injected quickly here
它刚刚被注入这里
right because app is being a little bit
对，因为应用程序有点
since all research service now and if we
因为现在所有的研究服务，如果我们
try our owners endpoint it should return
试试我们的所有者端点，它应该返回
us some list of owners which it's gonna
给我们一些业主名单
take a while to look for owners but
花一些时间寻找业主，但
eventually it should show up right we
最终它应该显示出来，我们
see the owners so this is it this is the
见业主，这就是这个
good life hover some hints
美好生活徘徊一些提示
or remote apps thank you for watching
或远程应用程序感谢您的观看
you
您